so my name is Daniel Stockton burger I
am the co-founders and the director of
research and development at North Acker
collective in addition to creatives and
technologies we also curate technologies
in the health and wellness human
optimization and neuro tech space
including safe space obviously Abed is a
foundational part of sleep optimization
I met Klaus here at the bulletproof
conference two years ago and I
introduced to the tsamina bed then
they've asked me was speaking about it
and I've had the tsamina system for
about a year and a half and you know
there's a lot of good organic mattresses
in the market good sleep systems I mean
it's not a price point that everybody
can do but if you can it clearly does
exist in a world of itself as far as
quality of sleep systems in terms of
having a mattress and a clear bed
novio see or compete against things that
has resistance to mites resistance to
mold the EMF RF mitigation that's built
into the system the Orthopaedic of the
system it's all extremely well designed
by people that have deep knowledge of
sleep science and environmental sciences
related to sleep for a good sleep
environment you still have to address
the temperature of the room the darkness
of it ambient noise is lots of other
things and of course it's not going to
solve apnea or knock Toria or other
sleep issues and you need to address but
as far as having you know every
optimally rejuvenative environment for
where you're going to spend a third of
your life it's awesome that's why I
invested in it is most health things
take that time and most of us are pretty
busy and so taking the extra time to be
in sauna or exercising or like we do it
cuz it's important but increasing the
quality of sleep even if you increase it
by a percent but then over the course of
eight hours a night over the course of
life is a big deal with no net time
added so yeah I think this Amin is a
great system